<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fuktigt som Helvete</title>
    <description>My personal blog where I generally talk about things too boring for anyone but myself.</description>
    <link>/conorolive/</link>
    <atom:link href="/conorolive/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 03:53:05 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 03:53:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jankare</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So as we wait for the questionably slow Edhesive MOOC to begin many weeks after this AP Computer Science class has already began, I decided to
work on something instead of doing the dreaded task of copying &quot;Hello World&quot; Java programs out of our outdated textbooks (such as having Windows XP in
their image examples). I didn&#39;t want to try and attempt some of the larger projects I had in mind since they seemed a bit daunting for something to try and 
tackle in a shorter amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project idea that I decided to do was one that (admittedly) has definitely been done before, but is proving to still be an interesting learning experience
for me, if nothing else comes of it. The basic idea behind it isn&#39;t that complicated: Use a simple k-means clustering algorithm to cluster 3D RGB values from an
image into colors that are representative of the rest of the image. One reason this could be useful, is for theming reasons (say, making your terminal colors
match your desktop wallpaper). Image segmentation actually does have a lot of other uses too, mainly in the area of computer vision (which could be a whole
other post), but nothing that my program is going to ever attempt to tackle.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 05:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/conorolive/2015/09/07/man-must-explore/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/conorolive/2015/09/07/man-must-explore/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
